[Music]
Manmadarasa Manmadarasa Kanni Valakare Kannula Lesa Kannula Lesa
What are
you doing? Who are you?
My love, this is my house, who are you? It was you who
told me to come to house number 13. It was you who
told me to come to get my ears pierced. It was you. I am the one who
pierced my ears. Is that so? Yes, yes,
tell me who pierced my ears.   Do you know what
our daughter is doing? Is
it because she has already had her ears and nose pierced? Is it because she
is being told to do it again? Is
it old-fashioned or the latest fashion
?
What is it?
Piercing the navel.
Oh, sinful, the bond between a mother and her child is like a umbilical cord
.  Are
you thinking of having fun by piercing the ring?   Did
I ever say that?
I said she's our daughter.
I just said she's our daughter.  Did I
say I'm a bad girl? If so, then that's it.
Today it's Karnataka,
tomorrow it's Andhra Pradesh, on the fourth day it's Kerala. That's
not enough.
You're the one who's here.
[Screaming] You're the one who's here.
[Music]
Hey, we're all in the village, we're not going to put wet cloths on
chickens.
Do you know what I'm seeing? You chicken thief. I
won't stand for three minutes.
Sir, stop the car and move it a little,
sir, please.
Oh, who is the Pope?
Hey, what's up?
Koyyalo Kuyyalo, Kumarathappa Kuyyaloi's
song is powerful.
Koyyalo or Koyyalo,
thanks sir.   Thank you
very much.
What is it?  Thank you, if you
were that arrogant fat person, you would be telling us the story of your car and making us laugh
.  Why?
Will your feet hurt if you get off?  Sir, give both of these guys a
heads up and get started
.  The body has a boil on it
.  See if there's a little more information.   They
both lay in the car, like watermelons going to the market.
Something.
Someone?
[Music]
Oh my, run.  That's why I was
there to push the cart for you.
I apologize then.
I escaped by stealing.  I'm sorry, I don't
know what your car is like.  I'm a [ __ ], I'm a fish
Maybe he's brushing his teeth, don't you see
there? A beautiful girl,
Iyengar, has come to make a bakery. Let's
see.
Hey, there are a lot of customers coming to our shop
.  Buy it, buy it, buy it,
buy it, what is it?
Three-pocket twist,
one-pocket waistband.  Wow,
this all seems
like a scam.
Is this a pot?
Later, Baru Kamakshi became a silver merchant.
So you only
go out on Fridays?
Okay, okay, take the list.  1 kg of
metti, 3/4 kg of nookuthi, 1/4 kg of
kammal.
Look at this, it has acid mixed in it.
Take it and pour it on top.  It will turn into blood
.  Who wants it?  What should I do for
you?
We have just moved into the house opposite.  My name is Kanmani.  My name is
Nilaveni.
My name is gold, Sirena, lion.
Oh, lion.
As soon as you get here, go to Vampalli
.  Will the crane eat the fish or not? Will the fish
eat the crane? The man eats both.
What do you want now? I want grace.
The devil rides a bicycle.
Which one should I take?
Grace should come to me now. If you want grace, go straight to the temple pond and worship the Lord,
or I
will trample you. You shouldn't talk to me like that. That's how I will talk to you. You
don't respect me even a little. You were telling me that.
Why did my brother tell you?
Look at the moon and the face. You went to the tin and
called me gold.
[Screaming]
Hey, is there any gold in you?
People are coming and going. Don't you want me to? I don't know
what you're doing. I've been
destroying you.
Oh, is it because you stole from me all these days?
Who is watching me? Who is
stealing from my house? What am I, a thief? I don't
even have the right to be honest in this house.
What have you done to me? You gave me a
silver shop, a
gold
Then 450
families came and gave me 50 and
talked about sex.
What's wrong with you? What's wrong with you? You don't want to
talk about your relationship, what's wrong with you? What's wrong with you? There are
80 acres in Pollachi.
You came with 40
acres. I've already taken
40 acres.
Your father hurriedly built four small houses.
My father was patient and
built only one small house. That's because of the little house. He doesn't talk
about my father. He
talks about my father. [Screaming]
Right, one hand, brother, you
all are one.  The reason for all this is
my grandfather.  Hey, big daddy,
I'll put it on you, big daddy [screaming],
leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, if you want to go, let it go
.
That mango farmer is
taking care of us for me.  I want to poke my eye.
Hey, what are you staring at?
Papa, I don't like red dresses.  That's why a dog's
eyes only see black and white
.
Do you know the color of the color?   Do
n't worry, I'll tell you.
Hey, don't make a sound.  If you hit all these gallows, your
skull will
crack.
Who is here?  Guests who came to our area
.  Go and chase them away.
Oh, I understand. I understand. Too bad I
didn't know that girl and came wearing a red dress
.  However,
you are chasing a girl with the same leg,
where is the same leg? [Laughter]
Now you ran away,
didn't you run away? 1:2 legs are one leg,
how can you run away?   Wait, I'll
tell you something.
No, it looks like they ran away.
I
came here with my sister-in-law, jumping and jumping.  Because the clothes are
tied, today your feet won't touch your bird,
wing wing, you are right,
you go, wing, wing, the same leg
Hey, shall we both
play then?
Adinga is a similar house.  Run away
.
Oh,
hey
Nothing.  Do you know
how beautifully the housewife limps in opposition
?
Avada, she has the same guard
.  Only a lame person can dance.
Who says it's the same?   It's
our time.
Hey, I saw a man with two legs, and I saw the same thing with both eyes
.
Hey, what happened to your family
?  If you talk about your father, they'll beat you up
.  Do you play with your two-
year-old child at the same time
?   It's the
same time.
Let's start.  Come on, let's go inside and
meet.  Everything you see with your eyes, O
chief, does not belong to your eyes, does not
belong to your eyes, A
pearl with eyes,
you will never leave my eyes, you will never leave me
[Music] Right, right   I
will leave you with one eye and two.   Are
you two free?
I left.  Kanmani,
hey Kanmani, my
mother is calling.  I went, "Hey,
Kanmani, you can ride a bicycle, I'm a cyclist,
who's going to teach me?"
I am not here.   Are
you?
Do you know how to ride a bicycle?
Come on, I know how to ride a bicycle.
Write down a list of what you know how to drive and go
drive it. Car, lorry, bus, ride,
airplane, etc.?
Do you know how to ride a bicycle?
Why don't you just
drive around asking questions?
You know how to ride a bicycle, so why do you have to sit on
top of me and ride?
I'm not ready to throw you over to someone else and
go to the murderous pit.  Listen to me
.
You drive first.
Push.   Look at
this.  The
sky has not changed from the day it arrived until this day.   The
man has changed.
[Music]
What is Bell doing here, what kind of biryani do you have there? There
are four parcels here.
They said that the child was a Saiva child.   Let's go
buy some biryani.
Hour.
[Music]
What's in the bell basket?   Let's
go buy some curry.
Hey, what's the dog doing after the vegetables
?  If there is meat, it will go.  Is that
pure vegetarianism?
Hey Neelaveni Anna, I bought some balcova
.  I'm in a race, come on,
Saika.
I asked, "Is it balcova?" Oh, you idiot, you can
get balcova at the biryani shop.
Ah, that's
my leg.  One leg for me,
one leg for you.  [Laughter]
If I saw a leg, I would cry for days
.
I'm eating a bad chicken, and I'm throwing up
.  Did you believe what I said, oh
dear, what do you want? How can you come up?
I'll smoke it. Let
your mother come. Let me know about this chicken
biryani and cigarettes. Hey,
my father, do you eat leg pizza? The
name of biryani here is
palkova.
You can only make Italian rice. You can make
beer buttermilk. They ca
n't make biryani palkova. Hey, it's you.
[Clearing throat] I don't know
why this is happening at home. When
I was in 12th grade, my friends tricked me into
eating it by saying it was a cheap army. I stuck the taste on my tongue and kept eating it
.
Is there a plastic bag for each?
Two packages a day.
If a package costs ₹40, how can he even happily marry you, who earns ₹2400-4500 a month
?  This is
not something that the person who is going to tie him up should worry about.  Why is he
making a fuss?
I don't eat anything all day.  Just
one day a week.  Four days a month.   It's only
₹320 for eight items.  If you
ask for ₹320 per month for a maid,
you will be fine.  Let's just drink from my hand
.  I am raising a family
.
Same peeling.  Besides that,
did you know that there is a fast on Saturdays, not eating on Saturdays?
What's happening to my body after fasting on Saturday and getting fully fit on Sunday?
Both of them are married and have children, so I'm
counting the money like a baby.
I'm in your place, so what's going on here? Don't talk,
you said there's no flood.
Wow, my leg piece.
Hey, come here
.   Come on, man
.  Mouth [laughter]
Hey, come here, come here [cough].
What are you asking for, leg pizza, and that's Angadam
biryani, lie [laughter], tell me something else, you idiot
.   Go to the
temple bells to cast the Kovapatta bell.
Anna's partner, the bell is ringing, the
bell is like a cow's neck, the mother-in-law's
neck is now ringing, the
pearl has fallen down, the conch shell is a
child's anklet, the bell is a
flower, the actor played the role of the head, the bell is ringing, I'm
leaving, the bell is coming to win
the little one, the bell is fading,
where is my couple, the bell is calling, the bell is ringing,
what is
it, the bell is ringing
What song do you want?
Kamal Haasan will sing in the Gunavu Cave,
do you know how to sing that song?
When will you see my dear lover?
The letter I am writing to you, my dear, is it a letter that I am writing to you? I am writing to
you. When I think of
writing it, I am at a loss for words. When I
look at you, the poem is beautiful.
But when I think of writing it, one, two, three, mani, mani,
another song, sing, sing, sing, buy, buy, we are
waiting for you.
[Laughter] Are
you the only person in the world who sends a reason for an ordinary ear piercing ceremony and organizes it like a grand festival? Yes, who will pierce my ears? How
old is my father?
70 70 Yes, he
wanted to pierce his nose at a young age. He couldn't, that's why he is piercing it now. Oh, his mother wanted to pierce her nose. She is
70 years old. She is a normal person.
She is a normal person. You are not an ordinary son. The
mother's son is the one who
does not break her mother's word. You are the head who protected her. I am
piercing my nose.
Good.  Time is running out, come on,
good time is running out,
what is this? [Screaming]
You said you wanted to pierce someone's nose,
why are you telling me to get a nose pierced?
How else can I tell you to get a nose pierced without a nose piercing? Don't get a nose pierced
here.
[Screaming]
What, moms, are you thinking so seriously?
What's the matter?
I see a ₹5000 note in the palace.
Can you find ₹5000?
When?
Last night.
What kind of uncle are you, a union leader for 5,000 people?  I
don't know how to deposit ₹5000.  Don't you know?   Did
anyone find the person who took it or
not?
Found it.  Then why
should I throw it away and buy some money?
What kind of owner is it? If you have a little bit of money,
what kind of big owner is it? Go and
take care of your own family and beat him up, uncle, and throw him away
.  After you said it yourself, what was your
idea, uncle? I took it. I took it.
Why didn't you tell me first? Uncle, I was just joking and
looking at it. I
couldn't do anything.
What did you do with the money you took?
I bought silver for ₹5000.
There was a small problem.
What a problem.
Chetiya,
my machine has been stolen from Singapore
.
I will give you this ₹50,000 silver for ₹5000.  We
don't need the police, it's just a problem now, go away
.  Are you afraid of that?   I'll
write "I sowed" and you
write "I bought".  So,
write this correctly too.
Then what would you have written
?
Your shopkeepers are always
asking the same thing.
Are you asking?  Is our merchant very
intelligent?
Sign.   I
bought this money from my father
[laughter] and
this is a beautiful red.
What is this for?   For
being deceived.
Okay then.   Maybe the
groom should have left some of the stolen money
.
Leave it and buy a similar brick for 5000.
Don't stop.
Hey, stop, uncle.  [Laughter]
Hey, wait.   Don't stop
.   Don't stop
.  Hey uncle, my
father is dead.
Why is Neelaveni standing in the sun?   I've been
waiting for you.
What's the matter with me?
My glass fell into that tank, can you
take some?   Did
your earring fall into this tank?
What is this for you?  I will even jump into the middle of the ocean
.  Now, Papa, I won't
let you go without taking it. You're a blue bird.
What's so funny?
This is our home's septic tank.   The
septic tank is
fine, but our tank itself is what it is.
This is all a trade secret.
Peel it like we peel our golden soil and take your skin
[music]
Father, this is the
last straw, this is the best peel.
[Laughter]
How did you get clean after being beaten?
Thank you very much.   I did
n't take it at all, but I said thank you
.
That's what I took.
What?
The sewer is
now empty, and the
sewer has been empty for ten days.
If you call the corporation, they
ask for ₹50.  That's why I called you and made a
small promise to see you in person.  But you are
very good, you started very quickly, you are a
good boy, you are a sinner, you have
shown us a lot, you have made us a fool, what are you, I
know one thing or the other, what do you want, will you
marry me or not, I will
marry you, when did you dance at the
door of your house,
you also danced, sang, talked and
laughed, everything was a lie, come on, sir, sir, don't
tie me, I will tie this
rope around your neck, I will
make her my bride.   Do
n't worry, there's a big 40-acre park here
.  I'll change that for you
.
Oh, sinful man, hurry up and tie a
necklace around that beggar's neck. I,
man, love you.
Then hit me on the head and swear to me
.
Seriously,
why are you worried about this?  If I give you ten rupees, you'll turn the
plate upside down and go
.  What a lucky charm for ten zodiac signs
.
What did you say, Talina? What are you kidding me about
?  Every girl has a fence, and
I am a Tamil Nadu beggar.
Come and
raise a family. Uncle, uncle, just sing a big song.
Everyone runs away. What happened? I tied a thaliya and
deceived you. I tied a thaliya and
beggar. If you are so greedy, I
will come to the house where the beggar is from. I will add four idlis to it.